So the name of today's number one company is
ICICI LBRD General Insurance.  The
stock price of the company is currently
trading at ₹1822.  The company has
announced the final dividend today
which is going to be ₹7. Since this is the
final dividend, the recorded dividend has
not been announced yet.  We will update you as soon as the company
announces it.
Along with this, the company has also announced the results.
You will get to see the results on our Telegram channel.
So let's talk
about the second number company.  The name of the company
is ICICI Principal L Insurance LED
and the stock price of the company
is currently trading at ₹567.  The company is going to
give a dividend of 85 paise which is going to be the final
dividend.  This too has
not been announced on record yet.  So let's talk
about the third number company.   The
name of the company is Cap TNOST LED.  The stock
price is currently
trading at ₹535.  The company is going to
give bonus shares in the ratio of 1:1.  The
record date for bonus shares has been announced.  The
record date and ex-date is going to be 21st of
April.  And at number four
is Shai Industries Limited stock price is
currently trading at ₹73.  The company
will supply the stock in the ratio of 1:10.  One share will become
10 shares.  The record date and
ex-date will be on the ninth of May.  And the
name of the fifth number company is Orient Cemented.   The
stock price is currently
trading at ₹358.  The company is going to
give a dividend of 50 paise.
No recorded announcement has been made for dividend.  So let's
talk about the sixth number company.  The
name of the company is Infosed
Limited.  The share price of the company is currently
trading at ₹6735.  The company is going to
split the stock in the ratio of 1:5.  One
share is going to be five shares.
Recordate and X date have arrived.   The
record date and ex-date will be on the seventh of May.
So the name of the seventh number company is
Cfin Homs LED stock price is currently
trading at ₹665.  The company will
announce dividend and result on 23rd of
April and the name of the eighth number company is
Mahindra & Mahindra stock price is currently
trading at ₹2644. The company will
announce dividend and result on 2nd of
April and the name of the ninth number company is
TL Patfs LED stock price is
trading at ₹485. The company will
announce dividend and result on 24th of
April. The name of the 10th number company is
Trent Limited stock price is currently
trading at ₹4870.  The company will
announce dividend and result on 29th of
April and at 11th position Kotak
Mahindra Bank LED stock price is
trading at ₹218. The company will
announce dividend and result on 3rd of May.
So at number 12 is Axis Bank LED
stock price, it is
trading at ₹112.  The company is going to
announce dividend and results on
24th of April.  So the name of the 13th number company
is AU Sal Finance Bank LED stock
price is currently
trading at ₹575.  The company is going to
announce dividend and result on 2nd
of April and is at 14th position. Shilt
Technologies LED stock price is currently
trading at ₹5632.  The company
is about to announce bonus shares.  The Board
of Directors meeting will be held on 21st April.
And at number 15 is Supreme
Industries Limited.  The stock price is currently
trading at 3378.  The company will
announce dividend and results on 24th of
April.  Vardha Special Steeled is at 16th position.  The
stock price is trading at ₹22.  The
company will announce dividend and results on
2nd of April and at 17th
position Federal Bank Limited stock
price is currently trading at ₹190.   The
company is going to announce dividend and results on
30th of April.  As soon as the
companies announce the results and
for live news, you
can follow us on Telegram.  The name of our Telegram channel
is Market Easy.